<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beginner on Risk &amp; Compliance Labs</title><link>/categories/beginner.html</link><description>Recent content in Beginner on Risk &amp; Compliance Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/beginner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Start the Workshop</title><link>/1-start-workshop.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 07:41:43 +1000</pubDate><guid>/1-start-workshop.html</guid><description>To start the workshop, follow one of the following depending on whether you are;
running the workshop on your own (in your own account),
or
attending an AWS hosted event (using AWS provided hashes)</description></item><item><title>Getting to Know the Console</title><link>/2-know-the-console.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 15:34:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>/2-know-the-console.html</guid><description>Login to your AWS Account If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, logon to your AWS account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an account, go to Start Workshop.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get to know the AWS Management Console
The AWS Management Console is a web application that comprises and refers to a broad collection of service consoles for managing Amazon Web Services. When you first sign in, you see the console home page.
Along the top menubar you will see a few important elements we will use often.</description></item><item><title>Accessing AWS Compliance Reports</title><link>/3-aws-compliance-reports.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/3-aws-compliance-reports.html</guid><description>In this workshop you will access AWS Artifact and download a compliance report and work through guidance on how to interpret the report. This workshop is a great place to start if you are new to AWS, it mixes a bit of hands-on with supporting theory.
Duration The lab should take approximately 30 minutes to complete.
Learning Outcome This workshop provides an introduction to compliance at AWS including the Shared Responsibility Model.</description></item><item><title>Detective Controls with Config</title><link>/4-detective-controls-config.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/4-detective-controls-config.html</guid><description>In this workshop we will use three AWS Config and AWS Config Rules to demonstrate how to automate controls, in this case, the controls will check the configuration of an Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket. The same approach can be applied to many AWS services.
Duration The lab should take approximately 45 minutes to complete.
Outcome By the completion of this lab you will have an understanding of the AWS Config Service and and understanding of the dashboard and timelines.</description></item><item><title>Patching Controls with Systems Manager</title><link>/6-patching-controls-ssm.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/6-patching-controls-ssm.html</guid><description>In this workshop you will be introduced to immutability of instances, and use AWS Systems Manager to inventory the operating systems and software running in the environment, identify patching requirements, and set up a corrective controls which will patch the selected instances.
Duration The lab should take approximately 60 minutes to complete.
Outcome Learn to apply automated controls to patching and about the different approached for Immutable and non-Immutable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Determine the current OS versions</title><link>/6-patching-controls-ssm/3-current-os.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/6-patching-controls-ssm/3-current-os.html</guid><description>In this step we will use AWS Systems Manager - Inventory to determine the operating systems versions how many instances are running each operating systems.
1. Go to AWS Systems Manager - Inventory Select Systems Manager from the AWS Console.
In the navigation pane, choose Inventory.
If you can only see the AWS Systems Manager home page, you may need to click on the menu icon (☰) in the top left to open the navigation pane, and then choose Inventory.</description></item><item><title>Set patch baselines</title><link>/6-patching-controls-ssm/4-set-patch-baselines.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/6-patching-controls-ssm/4-set-patch-baselines.html</guid><description>Now that we have enabled inventory and gained insight into the environment, let&amp;rsquo;s start on patching Patch Manager.
To understand how Patch Manager works it important to understand two key concepts; patch groups and patch baselines.
Patch baseline - a set of patches and software versions which together represent the patch standard or baseline. This baseline will become obsolete when new patches are released. Patch group - a set of instances (virtual servers) that are to be patched to the same standard.</description></item><item><title>Review compliance</title><link>/6-patching-controls-ssm/5-review-compliance.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/6-patching-controls-ssm/5-review-compliance.html</guid><description>Now that you have set the Patch Baseline for your two Patch Groups (windows-app-patch-group and linux2-app-patch-group) you have can use Patch Manager to compare the instances in the Patch Groups against the standards defined. Where the patch levels on the instances in the Patch Groups do not meet the Patch Baseline they will be marked as not compliant.
1. Run Patch Manager Scan From Patch Manager select Patch Now
Click Patch now</description></item><item><title>Create a maintenance window</title><link>/6-patching-controls-ssm/6-maintenance-window.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>/6-patching-controls-ssm/6-maintenance-window.html</guid><description>AWS Systems Manager Maintenance Windows let you define a schedule for when to perform potentially disruptive actions on your instances such as patching an operating system, updating drivers, or installing software or patches. These may require Systems Manager to perform a restart so these actions should be scheduled appropriately.
Create a maintenance window which you will use to patch the Windows and Amazon Linux 2 instances. The details of the maintenance window details such as time, duration, frequency are all up to you.</description></item></channel></rss>