<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beginner on Risk &amp; Compliance Labs</title><link>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/categories/beginner/</link><description>Recent content in Beginner on Risk &amp; Compliance Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/categories/beginner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Start the Workshop</title><link>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/1-start-workshop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2020 07:41:43 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/1-start-workshop/</guid><description>To start the workshop, follow one of the following depending on whether you are;
running the workshop on your own (in your own account),
or
attending an AWS hosted event (using AWS provided hashes)</description></item><item><title>Getting to Know the Console</title><link>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/2-know-the-console/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 15:34:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/2-know-the-console/</guid><description>Login to your AWS Account If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, logon to your AWS account. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have an account, go to Start Workshop.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get to know the Management Console
The AWS Management Console is a web application that comprises and refers to a broad collection of service consoles for managing Amazon Web Services. When you first sign in, you see the console home page.
Along the top menubar you will see a few important elements we will use often.</description></item><item><title>Accessing AWS Compliance Reports</title><link>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/3-aws-compliance-reports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/3-aws-compliance-reports/</guid><description>In this lab you will access AWS Artifact and download a compliance report and work through guidance on how to interpret the report.
This lab is a great place to start if you are new to AWS and mixes a bit of hand on with supporting theory.
AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS’ security and compliance reports and select online agreements.</description></item><item><title>Detective Controls with Config</title><link>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/4-detective-controls-config/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 15:17:40 +1000</pubDate><guid>http://paulJRCurtis.github.io/risk-lab-site/4-detective-controls-config/</guid><description>In this lab we will use three AWS Config rules to demonstrate how to check the configuration of an Amazon Simple Storage Service (Amazon S3) bucket.
AWS Config is a service that enables you to assess, audit, and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources. Config continuously monitors and records your AWS resource configurations and allows you to automate the evaluation of recorded configurations against desired configurations.
With Config, you can review changes in configurations and relationships between AWS resources, dive into detailed resource configuration histories, and determine your overall compliance against the configurations specified in your internal guidelines.</description></item></channel></rss>